// QUESTIONS AND ANSWERS ARRAY - App.jsx, helperFunctions.js
const QandA_Array = {
  subject: "Mental health",
  numOfQuestions: 3,
  scorePerCorrectAnswer: 10,
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Which of the following are real illnesses?",
      answers: ["Diabetes", "Anxiety", "Flu", "All of the listed"],
      correct: "All of the listed",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of these symptoms can happen if you are depressed?",
      answers: [
        "Don't feel hungry",
        "Constant fatigue",
        "Lowered sex drive",
        "All of the listed",
      ],
      correct: "All of the listed",
    },
    {
      question: "How to tell if someone has an anxious disorder?",
      answers: [
        "Has bad breath",
        "Untidy",
        "Great speaker",
        "Doesn't like to go out",
      ],
      correct: "Doesn't like to go out",
    },
    {
      question: "What is assertiveness?",
      answers: [
        "A type of disease",
        "A type of problematic behavior",
        "Good communication style",
        "None of the listed",
      ],
      correct: "Good communication style",
    },
    {
      question: "Agitation is?",
      answers: [
        "A type of Greek yoghurt",
        "A form of passive inexpedient behavior",
        "A positive statement",
        "Cummulative capabilities potential",
      ],
      correct: "A form of passive inexpedient behavior",
    },
    {
      question: "What is demophobia?",
      answers: [
        "An unnatural fear of a crowd of people",
        "A fear of democracy",
        "Overwhelming fear of a certain demographic",
        "None of the listed",
      ],
      correct: "An unnatural fear of a crowd of people",
    },
    {
      question: "Depression is?",
      answers: [
        "A state of utter hardship",
        "An uncommon mental health disorder",
        "A state of listlessness, helplessness and hopelessness",
        "None of the listed",
      ],
      correct: "A state of listlessness, helplessness and hopelessness",
    },
    {
      question: "Who does depression hit harder?",
      answers: [
        "Young adults",
        "Men in general",
        "Women in general",
        "Old people",
      ],
      correct: "Women in general",
    },
    {
      question: "Destrudo is?",
      answers: [
        "A type of sword in Ancient Rome",
        "Energy of the instinct of life",
        "Energy of the instinct of death",
        "Energy of the instinct of war",
      ],
      correct: "Energy of the instinct of death",
    },
    {
      question: "What is a Diana complex?",
      answers: [
        "Unconscious repressed desire of a women to be a man",
        "Unconscious repressed desire of a child to be an adult",
        "Unconscious repressed desire of a man to be a woman",
        "None of the listed",
      ],
      correct: "Unconscious repressed desire of a women to be a man",
    },
    {
      question: "What is euphoria?",
      answers: [
        "A feeling of missing something",
        "A feeling of dizziness",
        "A feeling of lightness, pleasantness and exuberance",
        "A feeling of loneliness",
      ],
      correct: "A feeling of lightness, pleasantness and exuberance",
    },
    {
      question: "What is a phantasm?",
      answers: [
        "An objective real percieved reality",
        "A subjective unrealistic representation of something in the waking state",
        "A sense of dread",
        "A sense of being decieved",
      ],
      correct:
        "A subjective unrealistic representation of something in the waking state",
    },
    {
      question: "What is hedonism?",
      answers: [
        "A love and preference of pleasure and enjoyment",
        "A sense of joy from inflicting suffering",
        "A state of permanently altered mindset",
        "A preference towards good habits",
      ],
      correct: "A love and preference of pleasure and enjoyment",
    },
    {
      question: "What is a dendrophobia?",
      answers: [
        "A fear of insects",
        "A fear of dark places",
        "A fear of trees",
        "A fear of canines",
      ],
      correct: "A fear of trees",
    },
    {
      question: "How shoud we proceed if we feel like we have mental problems?",
      answers: [
        "Stay home and rest",
        "Seek a professionals help as soon as possible",
        "Try to resolve the issues yourself",
        "Deny that you have the problem",
      ],
      correct: "Seek a professionals help as soon as possible",
    },
    //   {
    //     question: "",
    //     answers: [],
    //     correct: ''
    //   },
  ],
};

export { QandA_Array };
